[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In a motel scene from the movie Planes, Trains  Automobiles, Steve Martins character goes into the bathroom to wash his face. What did he grab instead of a towel?", "correct_answer": "A pair of underwear", "incorrect_answers": ["A  T-shirt", "A wash rag", "A sock"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following musical artists produces noise music?", "correct_answer": "Xome", "incorrect_answers": ["Xmal Deutschland", "X", "XTC"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the grandmother in the 1987 movie Flowers in the Attic, played by actress Louise Fletcher?", "correct_answer": "Olivia Foxworth", "incorrect_answers": ["Corrine Dollanganger", "Cathy Dollanganger", "Carrie Foxworth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The fundamental book The C Programming Language was written in 1978 by BWK and what other computer scientist?", "correct_answer": "DMR", "incorrect_answers": ["DRM", "MDR", "RMD"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these natural disasters is known to hit the lands of North Korea on the regular?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Droughts", "Floods", "Typhoons"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these movies directed by Martin Scorsese was nominated for eleven Academy Awards, winning five of them?", "correct_answer": "The Aviator", "incorrect_answers": ["The Departed", "Goodfellas", "Raging Bull"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year was the very first Godzilla movie produced?", "correct_answer": "1954", "incorrect_answers": ["1962", "1960", "1959"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does quinunc mean?", "correct_answer": "A busybody", "incorrect_answers": ["A necessary thing", "A five-cornered star", "A prime example"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What medical term refers to the fear of horses?", "correct_answer": "Equinophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Heliophobia", "Iatrophobia", "Dendrophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the original title of  the movie Dont Tell Mom the Babysitters Dead?", "correct_answer": "The Real World", "incorrect_answers": ["Fast Food Family", "Wheres the Babysitter", "Summer Vacation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mountain Dew was invented in Marion, Virginia and first marketed in Knoxville, Tennessee.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This type of ant is considered the most venomous of all insects.", "correct_answer": "Jack jumper ant", "incorrect_answers": ["Western brown ant", "Bulldog ant", "Fire ant"]}]